试过了  但他们说我向公司撒了谎
Yes, but they said I lied to the company,
所以他们可以开除我
so they could fire me.
所以我才要起诉
That's why I'm suing.
硅谷是个小地方
Silicon Valley's a very provincial town.
出了这事我就找不到工作了
I can't get a job anywhere.
《雇员测谎保护法》
Well, The Polygraph Protection Act
可以保护雇员  避免他们被强制测谎
keeps an employer from forcing you to take a lie detector test,
但也有例外
but there are exceptions.
比如涉及偷窃时
Theft.
克里斯汀  这是我们的调查员  杰森
Uh, Kristen, this is our investigator Jason.
你好  但我没偷东西啊
Hi. But I didn't steal anything.
是的  但这是公司进行测谎的原因
Yes, but it was the reason for the polygraph.
他们发现你撒了别的谎  但是...
They caught you in another lie, but...
他们需要确凿的证据
They need corroborating evidence.
的确
Right.
除非他们已经掌握了相关证据
And they couldn't have fired her